naiku.net 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Naiku

This Privacy Policy was last modified on: April 9, 2018 (updated Naiku address)

Naiku is committed to the privacy and security of our participating users. Supplementing the various measures that each client takes to protect its own computing and user environment, Naiku guards the privacy and the security of your information.  This privacy policy applies to Web sites operated by Naiku (collectively, the “Sites”):

www.naiku.net  
support.naiku.net  
a.naiku.net  
q.naiku.net

**Information Collection**  
At the Sites, Naiku offers you the opportunity to request information and use our products, programs and services. We allow visitors to submit by email resume information in connection with our employment opportunities, and to request by email information about becoming a publishing partner. We may also collect the following types of personally identifiable information through the Sites: the email address of visitors, user-specific information regarding what pages visitors access or visit and other information that visitors to the Sites may submit, such as registration information. On some of our sites, Naiku also collects personally identifiable information such as names and product-use information such as a user’s answers to test questions.

Naiku also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Safari or Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac), the domain name of your Internet service provider (ISP) (e.g., Comcast) and your computer’s IP address.

**Collection of Information by Others**  
The Sites contain links to Web sites not controlled by Naiku (e.g., to our publishing partners’ Web sites), whose information practices may be different than ours. This privacy policy does not apply to Web sites of any other company or organization linked to a Naiku site. You should consult the other Sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

**Use of Information**  
Naiku use this information to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and other questions or comments you submit to us.

In an effort to provide the best quality services, Naiku may use data obtained in order to evaluate the use of the system and to obtain and understand statistical and other generalized information about its users and how to improve the features and functions of Naiku Platforms.

Naiku may utilize third-party services. Such services may include various analytics of system usage or system performance. At all times, such third parties will be required to maintain the confidentiality of the information with which they may come in contact and be prohibited from using the information for any other purpose than the purpose which is described above.

**Security**  
Naiku’s servers are housed in a data center with 24-hour, 365-day/year access and staffed to provide effective protection of all data as well as for maximum uptime and system protection.

Naiku reviews its technology safeguards and measures on a periodic basis and strives to ensure the privacy of any user’s online information.

**Privacy**  
The information obtained by Naiku will not be given, sold, rented, loaned, disclosed to or shared with any third party except when it may be necessary for Naiku to comply with applicable law as described below.

Naiku recognizes the importance of maintaining the highest standards of privacy protection and complies with current laws and regulations governing privacy protection for students and schools. Naiku does not market to children under 13 years of age and does not employ games, contests, or other measures to collect personal information from children. No information obtained will be shared with third parties. In addition, Naiku will continue to revise its policies in this area to maintain its legal compliance and use its reasonable efforts to institute “best practices” as they become available.

Naiku may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

Laws and their related regulations in this area may be reviewed by visiting the U.S. Federal Trade Commission’s website at http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html. Naiku currently complies with all laws and regulations established under current law, such as The Child’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) legislation and similar measures. You may also be interested in reviewing the Children’s Internet Protection Act: http://www.ifea.net/cipa.html.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
Naiku may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time so you should review this page periodically. Changes to the policy will be made effective upon providing you with a thirty (30) days notice. Notice will be provided by sending you an email at the address we have on file for you with your Account. The most up-to-date version will be posted with a “last modified” date on this webpage.

If you don’t agree to any changes, then you must provide us with written notice to [support@naiku.net](mailto:support@naiku.net) and we will automatically delete your account (including all related information), unless you notify us otherwise.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement, please contact us at: Naiku, 12100 Singletree Lane, Suite 185, Eden Prairie, MN 55344 or at [support@naiku.net](mailto:support@naiku.net).
